 Order Cancellation Policy: "Orders can be cancelled free of cost any time before the order status changes to 'Packed', typically within the first 2 minutes of placing the order. Once an order has been packed, it can no longer be cancelled through the app, since the rider is dispatched immediately after packing given Zepto's quick-delivery model. If a packed order cannot be delivered due to a Zepto-side issue (for example, rider unavailability), the order is auto-cancelled and fully refunded without any cancellation fee."