 Gift Cards: "Zepto gift cards are available in fixed denominations of INR 100, INR 250, INR 500, and INR 1000, and are delivered by email or SMS within minutes of purchase. Gift cards are valid for 1 year from the date of issue and carry no maintenance fees. Gift card balance can be combined with one other payment method at checkout but cannot be combined with another gift card in the same transaction. Gift card balance cannot be redeemed for cash except where required by law."